{"data":{"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"407","name":"Casey's Pub d/b/a The Red Corridor","address":"1830 Michigan Ave","zipcode":"48216","owner":"Kimberly Powers","licenseNumber":"202811","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","mostRecentLicenseDate":"4/28/2017","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Temporarily Closed","riskCategory":null,"reviewFrequencyDays":"365.0","geom":"0101000020E61000003423CF6A8BC454C0705834B9722A4540","inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"38517","establishmentid":"407","name":"Casey's Pub d/b/a The Red Corridor","inspectionDate":"2017-04-19T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"87","pcount":"2","pfcount":"6","ccount":"3","criticalcount":"8","noncritical":"3","correctedcritical":"7","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"38517","inspectionDate":"4/19/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"407","name":"Casey's Pub d/b/a The Red Corridor","violationCode":"3-501.17","violationDescription":"(A)  READY-TO-EAT, POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  prepared and held refrigerated for more than 24 hours in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT  shall be clearly marked at the time of preparation to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n(B)  A container of refrigerated, commercially prepared READY-TO-EAT POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  shall be clearly marked, at the time the original container is opened in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n\r\nA date marking system that does not exceed 7 days, including date of preparation, or opening is to be used. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"In house prepared ready-to-eat potentially hazardous  food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Improperly date marked","subProblem":"Longer than 7 days stored at 41 degrees f","location":"UPPER KITCHEN","subLocation":"In the Cooler(s)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-04-19T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide proper date marks as stated above."},{"inspectionid":"38517","inspectionDate":"4/19/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"407","name":"Casey's Pub d/b/a The Red Corridor","violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\r\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\r\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \r\n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\r\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"disposable, paper towels","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"UPPER KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Handsink","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-04-19T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide"},{"inspectionid":"38517","inspectionDate":"4/19/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"407","name":"Casey's Pub d/b/a The Red Corridor","violationCode":"4-302.12","violationDescription":"(A) FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES shall be provided and readily accessible for use in ensuring attainment and maintenance of FOOD temperatures as specified under Chapter 3. (Pf)   \r\n(B) A TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE with a suitable small-diameter probe that is designed to measure the temperature of thin masses shall be provided and readily accessible to accurately measure the temperature in thin FOODS such as MEAT patties and FISH filets. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Food thermometer(s)","subItem":"probe","problemDescription":"Not available","subProblem":"","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"Missing Digital Thermometer","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-04-26T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Make available at all times."},{"inspectionid":"38517","inspectionDate":"4/19/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"407","name":"Casey's Pub d/b/a The Red Corridor","violationCode":"4-204.112","violationDescription":"(A)  In a mechanically refrigerated or hot FOOD storage unit, the sensor of a TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE shall be located to measure the air temperature in the warmest part of a mechanically refrigerated unit and in the coolest part of a hot FOOD storage unit.\r\n(B)  Cold or hot holding EQUIPMENT used for POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD shall be designed to include and shall be equipped with at least one integral or permanently affixed TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE that is located to allow easy viewing of the device's temperature display (EXCEPT, heat lamps, cold plates, steam tables, or other equipment where it is not practical).\r\n(C)  TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES shall be designed to be easily readable.\r\n(D)  FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES and water TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES on WAREWASHING machines shall have a numerical scale, printed record, or digital readout in increments no greater than 1C or 2F in the intended range of use. (Pf)\r\n\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Thermometer(s)","subItem":"refrigeration","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"UPPER KITCHEN","subLocation":"Missing Thermometer(s)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-04-26T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide as required"},{"inspectionid":"38517","inspectionDate":"4/19/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"407","name":"Casey's Pub d/b/a The Red Corridor","violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"FRONT PREP AREA","subLocation":"Inside the Prep cooler","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-04-19T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard"},{"inspectionid":"38517","inspectionDate":"4/19/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"407","name":"Casey's Pub d/b/a The Red Corridor","violationCode":"6-301.11","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of 2 adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with a supply of hand cleaning liquid, powder, or bar soap. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Soap","subItem":"at handsink kitchen","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"UPPER KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Handsink","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-04-19T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide"},{"inspectionid":"38517","inspectionDate":"4/19/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"407","name":"Casey's Pub d/b/a The Red Corridor","violationCode":"6-202.11","violationDescription":"Except as otherwise approved, light bulbs shall be shielded, coated, or otherwise shatter-resistant in areas where there is exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; or unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Light shielding","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"In dishwash area","location":"UPPER KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Light fixture","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide adequate light shields and end caps or shatter-proof bulbs."},{"inspectionid":"38517","inspectionDate":"4/19/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"407","name":"Casey's Pub d/b/a The Red Corridor","violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"At the Test strips","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-04-26T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide as required"},{"inspectionid":"38517","inspectionDate":"4/19/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"407","name":"Casey's Pub d/b/a The Red Corridor","violationCode":"6-301.14","violationDescription":"A sign or poster that notifies FOOD EMPLOYEES to wash their hands shall be provided at all HANDWASHING SINKS used by FOOD EMPLOYEES and shall be clearly visible to FOOD EMPLOYEES.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Handwashing signage","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"UPPER KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Handsink","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-04-19T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide"},{"inspectionid":"38517","inspectionDate":"4/19/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"407","name":"Casey's Pub d/b/a The Red Corridor","violationCode":"MFL289.2129","violationDescription":"Sec. 2129. (1) All of the following food establishments shall employ a minimum of 1 managerial employee who is currently certified under a personnel certification program accredited by the American national standards institute, utilizing the conference for food protection standards:  (a) A food service establishment that is not any of the following:    (i) Operating under a temporary food service establishment license.  (ii) A vending machine location.     (b) An extended retail food establishment.  (c) Operated within a retail grocery.  (2) An individual certified under subsection (1) shall be recognized with full faith and credit by the state and all local units of government throughout the state.  (3) The department may promulgate rules to do all of the following:  (a) Develop requirements for retail food establishments to follow when employing certified food safety managers or personnel.  (b) Set a reasonable date for compliance with the requirements under subdivision (a) taking into consideration existing local personnel certification requirements.  (c) Establish certification fees necessary to implement, maintain, and track certified individuals directly or by contract. The department may annually adjust the schedule of fees to provide that the fee charged is sufficient to cover the cost of the certification tracking program.  (d) Implement and enforce the requirements described in subdivision (a).    (4) The certification program developed by the American national standards institute, as it exists on April 1, 2008 , is incorporated by reference. The department may adopt updates to the certification program accreditation standards in subsection (1) by rule.     (5) This section does not prohibit any local legislative body from implementing a food handler program, an employee health certification program, or a manager certification program, if it is not in conflict with this section.","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Missing","subProblem":"","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"At the PERSON IN CHARGE","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"inspectionid":"38517","inspectionDate":"4/19/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"407","name":"Casey's Pub d/b/a The Red Corridor","violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\r\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\r\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Plumbing system","subItem":"water line(s)","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"UPPER KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Three compartment sink","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"}]},{"inspectionid":"37309","establishmentid":"407","name":"Casey's Pub d/b/a The Red Corridor","inspectionDate":"2016-12-01T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"87","pcount":"0","pfcount":"0","ccount":"3","criticalcount":"0","noncritical":"3","correctedcritical":"0","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"37309","inspectionDate":"12/1/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"407","name":"Casey's Pub d/b/a The Red Corridor","violationCode":"6-501.11","violationDescription":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Physical facilities","subItem":"Floor(s)","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"UPPER KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Floor","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"inspectionid":"37309","inspectionDate":"12/1/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"407","name":"Casey's Pub d/b/a The Red Corridor","violationCode":"6-202.11","violationDescription":"Except as otherwise approved, light bulbs shall be shielded, coated, or otherwise shatter-resistant in areas where there is exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; or unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Light shielding","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"UPPER KITCHEN","subLocation":"Missing Light Shield(s)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide adequate light shields and end caps or shatter-proof bulbs."},{"inspectionid":"37309","inspectionDate":"12/1/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"407","name":"Casey's Pub d/b/a The Red Corridor","violationCode":"5-501.17","violationDescription":"A toilet room used by females shall be provided with a covered receptacle for sanitary napkins.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Covered waste receptacle(s)","subItem":"in public restroom","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"RESTROOM (WOMEN'S PUBLIC)","subLocation":"No Covered waste container","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide as required"}]}]}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"407"}}